An Inventory of the United States. Food Administration records XX066
Hoover Institution Archives
- Alphabetical file, 1901-1928, 1940-1942 (Folder 88-203,300-315, 420)
  - Hughs, H. J.
    See Grain Corporation files, Milling Division files
  - Humphreys, H.
  - Hungary.
    See Austria Hungary
  - Hurley, Edward N.
  - I correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 150: 15)
  - I correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 151: 1-3)
  - Ice., See 39-H (Folder 151)
  - Iceland, 1917-1918. (Folder 151: 4)
    Includes Great Britain-Iceland Agreement,
    - General, 1916-1919. (Folder 151: 5-7)
    - Beverages, 1917-1918 (Folder 151: 8)
    - Brazil, circa 1917 (Folder 151: 9)
    - Condiments, 1918 (Folder 151: 10)
    - Cotton, 1917 (Folder 151: 11)
    - Dairy products, 1911-1919 (Folder 151: 12)
    - Dutch East Indies, 1918 (Folder 151: 13)
    - Fats and oils, 1911-1918 (Folder 151: 14-16)
    - Feeding stuffs, 1917-1918 (Folder 151: 17)
    - Fish, 1911-1919 (Folder 151: 18)
    - Food, 1911-1918 (Folder 151: 19-20)
    - Fruit, 1911-1918 (Folder 151: 21)
    - Grain, 1914-1919 (Folder 151: 22)
    - Great Britain, France and Italy, 1914-1919 (Folder 151: 23)
    - Japanese foodstuffs, 1918 (Folder 151: 24)
    - Leather and hides, 1917 (Folder 151: 25)
    - Linseed, 1918 (Folder 151: 26)
    - Manganese.
      See Imports-Brazil
    - Meat and livestock, 1911-1918. (Folder 152: 1)
    - Neutrals, 1917 (Folder 152: 2)
    - Nuts, 1911-1918 (Folder 152: 3)
    - Policy, 1917 (Folder 152: 4)
    - Rice, 1911-1918 (Folder 152: 5)
    - Rubber, 1918 (Folder 152: 6)
    - Russia, Siberia, 1918 (Folder 152: 7)
    - Sugar, syrup, molasses, 1918 (Folder 152: 8)
    - Tobacco, 1918 (Folder 152: 9)
    - Vegetables, 1911-1918 (Folder 152: 10)
    - Wool, 1918 (Folder 152: 11)
  - India, 1917-1919 (Folder 152: 12)
  - Industrial Conservation, Evolution of Policies and Procedures, 1917-18, by Stella Stewart, 1941 (Folder 152: 13)
  - Influenza, 1918-1918 (Folder 152: 14)
    1938.
  - Insecticides.
    See Agricultural pests
  - Intelligence.
    See 32-H; 44-H
  - Inter-Allied Food Council Committee of Representatives, Minutes of Proceedings, I-IV July-December 1918.
    See International food controls
  - Inter-Allied Scientific Food Committee.
  - Interdepartmental Advisory Committee, minutes of meetings, 1917 (Folder 152: 15)
  - Interior Department, 1917-1919 (Folder 152: 16-18)
  - International Health Board, 1918. (Folder 152: 19)
    See also Public Health Service
  - Internment camps, 1917-1918 (Folder 152: 20)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1917-1919 (Folder 153: 1-2)
  - Introduction, Letters of, 1917-1919 (Folder 153: 3-5)
  - Inventions, 1918 (Folder 153: 6)
  - Inventory of furniture and office equipment not in use, 1919 (Folder 153: 7)
  - Iodine combination, 1918 (Folder 153: 8)
  - Ireland.
    See Great Britain, Ireland
  - Iron and ammonium citrate, 1918 (Folder 153: 9)
  - Irrigation, 1917-1918 (Folder 153: 10)
  - Italy, 1909-1918. (Folder 153)
    See also box 312
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 153: 11-13)
    - Agriculture and crops, 1917-1918 (Folder 153: 14)
    - Agriculture and food ministries [in the U.S.], Gaetano Pietra, Stefano Avonzo, Randolph Santini, 1917-1981 (Folder 153: 15)
    - Commissary General for Supply and Consumption of Food (Commissariato Generale per gli Approvvigionamenti e i Consumi), 1909-1918 (Folder 153)
      - General, 1909-1918 (Folder 153: 16-17)
      - Silvio Benigno Crespi, 1917-1918 (Folder 153: 18)
      - Silvio Benigno Crespi, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 154: 1)
      - Bread, flour, flour pastes, and grain, 1917-1918 (Folder 154: 2)
      - Dairy products, eggs, poultry, and fish, 1917-1918 (Folder 154: 3)
      - Durand, E. Dana, 1918 (Folder 154: 4)
      - Fats and oils, 1918 (Folder 154: 5)
      - Fruit and vegetables, 1918 (Folder 154: 6)
      - Meat and livestock, 1918 (Folder 154: 7-8)
      - Prices, 1917-1919 (Folder 154: 9)
      - Rations, 1917-1918 (Folder 154: 10)
      - Reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 154)
        - General, 1817-1918 (Folder 154: 11)
        - Charles A. Platt, 1918 (Folder 154: 12)
        - Frederic C. Walcott and James T. Bell, 1918 (Folder 154: 13)
      - Sugar, 1917-1918 (Folder 154: 14)
    - Commissary General of National Fuel (Commissariato Generale per i Combustibili), 1917-1918 (Folder 154: 15)
    - Correspondence with Italian government, 1918 (Folder 154: 16)
    - Cotton, 1918 (Folder 154: 17)
    - Embassy, Washington, Count V. Macchi di Cellere, 1917-1918. (Folder 154: 18)
      See also State Department, Personnel of Foreign Missions
    - Exports and imports, 1912-1918 (Folder 154: 19)
    - Fertilizers, 1917-1918 (Folder 154: 20)
    - Herron, George.
      See Italian Report
    - High Commissioner Francesco Quattrone, 1917-1918 (Folder 154: 21)
    - Italian report, 1913 (Folder 154: 22-23)
    - Mott, Col. T. Bentley.
      See Italian report
    - Post-War trade and reconstruction, 1918 (Folder 154: 24)
    - Wine and alcohol, 1917-1918 (Folder 154: 25)
  - J correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 155: 1-5)
  - Jackson, George.
    See Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence
  - Jackson, W. A.
  - Jacobs, Benjamin R.
  - Jago, William.
  - Jam, circa 1917 (Folder 155: 6)
  - James, E. Ibbitson.
  - James, E. W.
  - Jamaica.
  - Japan, 1911-1919. (Folder 155)
    See also Imports, Japanese foodstuffs, Shipping Board, Japanese Boats
    - General, 1917-1919 (Folder 155: 7)
    - Exports and imports, 1911-1919 (Folder 155: 8)
    - Food situation, 1917-1919 (Folder 155: 9)
  - Jensen, Alfred O.
    See Fletcher, Horace
  - Jerusalem artichoke.
    See Girasole
  - Jordan, David Starr, 1917-1918 (Folder 155: 10)
  - Jusserand, Jules.
    See France, French Embassy, Washington
  - Justice Department, Thomas Watt Gregory, 1917-1918 (Folder 155: 11-12)
  - Justiss, I. F.
  - Jute.
  - K correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 155: 13-16)
  - K correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 156: 1-3)
  - Kafir.
    See Grain, Kafir
  - Kellicott, William E.
    See 40-H
  - Kellogg, Douglas.
  - Kellogg, Frank B.
    See Congress, Senate
  - Kellogg, Vernon Lyman.
    See 27-H; France, USFA, Correspondence
  - Kennedy, Philip B.
  - Kent, William.
    See Tariff Commission
  - Kimball, K. P.
    See 18-H; 44-H
  - King, Clyde L.
  - Korea (Chosen), 1911-1918 (Folder 156: 4)
  - L correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 156: 5-15)
  - Labor, 1917-1941. (Folder 156)
    See also 33-H
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 157: 1-2)
    - Chinese, 1917-1918. (Folder 157: 3)
      See also Labor Relations in the United States..., by J. D. Edward, 1941
    - Labor Department, 1917-1918. (Folder 157: 4-5)
      See also Internment camps
    - William B. Wilson, 1917-1918 (Folder 157: 6)
    - Labor Relations in the United States, Summary of Historical Events in the World War Period, 1912-1920, by J. Donald Edwards, 1941 (Folder 157: 7)
    - War Labor Policies Board, Felix Frankfurter.
      See 33-H, Labor Statistics
  - Ladd, E. F.
    See 6-H, North Carolina
  - Lahey, H. J.
  - Lamborn, A. H. Co.
    See 30-H
  - Lane, Franklin K.
    See Interior Department
  - Lane Gertrude B.
    See 26-H
  - Lane, M. B.
    See 17-H
  - Lansing, Robert.
    See State Department
  - Larsen, L. A.
    See 3-H
  - Lasater, Ed. C., 1917-1918. (Folder 157: 8)
    See also 15-H
  - Laughlin, Irwin.
  - Law and legislation.
    See 14-H; War legislation
  - Lawrence, G. W.
    See 44-H; 21-H
  - Leases for Food Administration buildings.
  - Leather and hides, 1917-1919 (Folder 157: 9-10)
  - Leeward Islands.
  - Legge, Alexander.
    See War Industries Board, Requirements Division
  - Legislation.
  - Leggett, H. T.
  - Letters of introduction.
    See Introduction, Letters of
  - Lever, Asbury F.
    See Congress, House of Representatives
  - Lewis, C.
  - Liberia, 1918 (Folder 157: 11)
  - Liberty Loan.
  - License revocation.
  - Licenses.
    See 37-H; 40-H
  - Lichty, George E.
  - Lindley, Curtis H.
  - Linen.
    See Textile industry
  - Lingham, Fred J.
    See Grain Corporation file
  - Linseed.
    See Flax, Flaxseed, Linseed
  - Liquor.
    See Beer and liquor
  - Literary Digest, 1917 (Folder 157: 12)
  - Littlefield, Leland H.
  - Livestock, 1911-1919.
    See also 15-H; Leather and hides
    - Associations, 1917-1918 (Folder 157: 13)
    - Dossier, November 1917 (Folder 157: 14)
    - Comparative Statement of Receipts at Various Markets, September 1916 and 1917 (Folder 157: 15)
    - Reports, 1916-1920 (Folder 157: 16-18)
    - Receipts at stock yards, 1917-1918 (Folder 158: 1)
    - Cattle reports, 1917-1919 (Folder 158: 2-3)
    - Cattle in trade between the United States, Canada and Mexico, report, 1912-1916 (Folder 158: 4)
    - Cattle inspection for slaughter, 1917-1919 (Folder 158: 5)
    - Hogs, 1911-1918 (Folder 158: 6-8)
    - Sheep and goats, 1916-1918 (Folder 159: 9)
  - Livingston, Don.
    See 6-H; South Dakota
  - Local committees, 1918 (Folder 158: 10)
  - London Conference of Food Controllers.
    See International Food Controls file
  - Long, Breckinredge.
  - Long, Maurice.
    See France, Food Ministry
  - Loomis, H. M.
  - Lord, Isabel Ely.
  - Lowry, Frank A.
  - Lucy, Captain J. F.
    See 22-H; 32-H
  - Lumber.
    See Timber
  - Lusk, Graham.
    See 11-H; Advisory Committee on Alimentation
  - Luxburg Telegrams.
    See Argentina
  - M correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 158: 11-16)
  - M correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 159: 1-13)
  - McAdoo, W. G.
    See Railroad Administration, Treasury Department
  - McCarthy, Charles.
  - McCarty, George A.
    See 16-H
  - Macchi di Gellere, Count V.
    See Italy
  - McCormick, Medill.
  - McCormick, Vance.
    See War Trade Board
  - McDevitt, J. A.
  - McDowell, Charles H.
  - McDuffie, Duncan.
    See 10-H; 47-H
  - McFadden, George.
    See 7-H; War Trade Board
  - McFadden, Mrs. Lily C.
  - McGowan, Admiral Samuel.
    See 29-H; Navy Department
  - Macaroni, 1917 (Folder 160: 1)
  - Machinery, 1917 (Folder 160: 2)
  - Macy, W. K.
  - Madera, 1918-1919 (Folder 160: 3)
  - Mail resume.
  - Malt, 1917-1919 (Folder 160: 4)
  - Manchuria, 1918 (Folder 160: 5)
  - Manloc.
    See Food Substitutes, Statistical Bulletins
  - Maps, circa 1917 (Folder 160: 6)
  - Margarine, 1914-1919. (Folder 160: 7)
    See also Fats and oils
  - Markets, General, 1917-1918 (Folder 160: 8)
  - Markets, Meat, 1918 (Folder 160: 9)
  - Markets, Retail, 1918 (Folder 160: 10)
  - Maxim, Hudson, 1917 (Folder 160: 11)
  - Maxwell, R. C.
  - McIntosh, J. W., Lt. Col.
  - McLennan, Russell M.
  - McNear, George W., 1917-1919 (Folder 160: 12)
  - Meat, 1909-1919. (Folder 160)
    See also 15-H; Livestock
    - General, 1914-1919 (Folder 160: 13-14)
    - Consumption per capita, 1917-1918 (Folder 160: 15)
    - Frozen, 1918 (Folder 160: 16)
    - Preserved, 1917-1918 (Folder 160: 17-19)
    - Yields, 1917 (Folder 160: 20)
    - Beef, 1911-1919 (Folder 160: 21-23)
    - Beef, 1911-1919 (contd.) (Folder 161: 1)
    - Lamb, 1911-1918 (Folder 161: 2)
    - Mutton, 1911-1918 (Folder 161: 3)
    - Poultry, 1909-1918 (Folder 161: 4)
    - Rabbits, 1918 (Folder 161: 5)
  - Medical Instruction.
  - Medical questions, 1917-1918 (Folder 161: 6)
  - Meeker, Arthur.
    See 15-H
  - Mendel, Lafayette B.
    See Taylor, A. E., Correspondence
  - Merrill, C. R.
  - Merrill, Edwin G.
    See Great Britain, Food Administration, correspondence
  - Merrill, W. H.
  - Merritt, Ralph P.
    See 6-H California
  - Merz, Charles.
    See 12-H; 15-H; 30-H; 35-H
  - Metabolism.
    See Medical questions
  - Mexico, General, 1917-1918. (Folder 161: 7-8)
    See also 16-H; 39-H
  - Mexico, Exports and imports, 1911-1919 (Folder 161: 9-11)
  - Miles, Major James.
  - Military service.
    See Draft
  - Milk.
    See 18-H; 34-H; 35-H
  - Miller, John C.
  - Milling and Milling Questions.
    See Milling Division Files
  - Milne, W. A.
    See 5-H; 6-H
  - Mitchell, Sidney A.
    See 10-H; France, USFA, correspondence; Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence; Great Britain, Food Ministry, Rations; War Trade Board Switzerland, Federal Food Office
  - Molasses and syrup, 1917-1918 (Folder 161: 12)
  - Monnet, M.
  - Moore, Frances.
    See 23-H
  - Moran, W. H.
  - Morgan, H. H.
    See Cuba
  - Moritz, Benjamin.
  - Mosshart, Gertrude.
  - Mullendore, Wm. C.
  - Munitions, 1918 (Folder 161: 13)
  - Munn, John R.
  - N correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 161: 14-20)
  - N correspondence, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 162: 1-2)
  - Nansen, Fridtjof.
    See Norway, Norwegian Special Mission to the U.S.
  - Nardin, Wm. T.
  - National Emergency Food Garden Commission.
    See War Gardens
  - National Nonpartisan League, 1918 (Folder 162: 3)
  - National Research Council, 1917-1918 (Folder 162: 4)
  - National War Garden Commission.
  - National Wholesale Grocers' Association of the United States, 1917-1918 (Folder 162: 5-9)
  - Navy Department, 1917-1919 (Folder 162)
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 162: 10)
    - Josephus Daniels, 1917-1918 (Folder 162: 11)
    - Samuel S. McGowan, 1917-1918 (Folder 162: 12)
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1917-1919 (Folder 162: 13)
    - Naval Communication Service, Daily Radio Press Bulletin, 1918 (Folder 162: 14-16)
    - Naval Communication Service, Daily Radio Press Bulletin, 1918 (contd.) (Folder 163: 1-3)
    - Naval Intelligence Office, 1917-1918 (Folder 163: 4)
  - Needham, Enoch.
  - Netherlands, 1911-1919.
    See also East Indies, Dutch; Shipping, Dutch Legation
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 163: 5)
    - Agreements, 1917-1918 (Folder 163: 6-7)
    - Agriculture, Industry and Commerce Ministry (Landbouw, Nijverheid en Handel), 1911-1919 (Folder 163)
      - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 163: 8-9)
      - Bread and grain, 1912-1918 (Folder 163: 10)
      - Fats and oils, 1911-1919 (Folder 163: 11)
      - Prices, 1915-1919 (Folder 163: 12)
      - Rations, 1916-1919 (Folder 163: 13-15)
    - Economic and political conditions, 1918 (Folder 163: 16)
    - Exports and imports, 1911-1919 (Folder 164: 1-2)
    - Fuel, 1917-1919 (Folder 164: 3)
    - Trade with Germany, 1917-1918 (Folder 164: 4)
    - Legation, 1917-1918 (Folder 164: 5)
    - Overseas Trust, 1918-1919 (Folder 164: 10)
  - Neutrals, 1917-1919, 1940-1942. (Folder 164)
    - General, 1917-1919 (Folder 164: 6-7)
    - Correspondence regarding The Policy of the U.S. toward Neutrals, 1917-1918, by Thomas A. Bailey, 1940-1942 (Folder 164: 8-9)
  - Netherlands Oversea Trust, 1917-1918 (Folder 164: 10)
  - New South Wales.
    See Australia
  - New York Food Board.
    See 6-H, New York
  - New Zealand, 1917-1919. (Folder 164: 11)
    See also Tasmania
  - Newfoundland, 1917-1918 (Folder 164: 12)
  - Nicaragua, 1918 (Folder 164: 13)
  - Nicholson, J. L.
    See Federal Trade Commission; 47-H
  - Nitrates, 1917-1918. (Folder 164: 14)
    See also Chile, Nitrate Industry, Fertilizers, 26-H
  - Nitric Acid.
    See Nitrates
  - Noel M.
  - Noncombatants, 1918 (Folder 164: 15)
  - North Packing and Provisions Co., See 44-H
  - Norway, 1917-1919
    - General, 1918-1919 (Folder 164: 16)
    - Legation, 1917-1919 (Folder 164: 17)
    - Agreement.
      See Norwegian Special Mission to the United States
    - Agriculture, crops, etc, 1917-1918 (Folder 164: 18)
    - Exports and imports, 1917-1919 (Folder 164: 19-20)
    - Finance, 1918 (Folder 164: 21)
    - Food Control Board (Provianteringsraadet), 1917-1919
      - General, 1917-1919 (Folder 165: 1)
      - Fats and oils, 1917-1918 (Folder 165: 2)
      - Prices, 1917-1918 (Folder 165: 3)
    - Norwegian Government Food Commission (New York), 1918 (Folder 165: 4)
    - Norwegian Special Mission to the United States, Fridtjof Nansen, 1917-1918 (Folder 165: 5)
    - Shipping, 1917 (Folder 165: 6)
    - Trade with Germany, 1917-1918 (Folder 165: 7)
  - Nutrition.
  - Nuts, 1918 (Folder 165: 8)
  - O correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 165: 9-11)
  - Oats.
    See Grain-Oats
  - O'Brien, Frederick.
  - Oils and Seeds.
    See Fats, Oils and oil seeds
  - Olives and olive oil, 1918-1919. (Folder 165: 12)
  - Oleomargarine.
    See Fats and oils
  - Onions.
    See Vegetables, Onions
  - Osborn, I. S.
  - Osborn, William.
    See 12-H Advertising
  - Osborne, Rachelle H.
    See 24-H
  - Owen, Wm. H.
    See World Trade Board, Foreign Agents, Stockholm
  - Owens, W. B.
    See 37-H
  - P correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 165: 13-18)
  - P correspondence, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 166: 1-7)
  - Pacific Islands, 1912 (Folder 166: 8)
  - Packers, Packing industry, 1917-1919. (Folder 166: 9-11)
    See also 15-H; Livestock, Meat
  - Padilla, Mr. (Folder 166)
    See 44-H; Puerto Rico
  - Panama, 1918 (Folder 166: 12)
  - Paper and pulp industry, 1918-1919 (Folder 166: 13-14)
  - Paraguay, 1917-1918 (Folder 166: 15)
  - Pardee, John S.
  - Parker, Edwin B.
    See War Industries Board, Priorities
  - Patton, Captain W. S.
  - Peanuts and peanut products, 1917-1919 (Folder 166: 16)
  - Pearl, Raymond.
    See 17-H; Great Britain, USFA, Correspondence
  - Peden, E.
    See 6-H; Texas
  - Peek, George N., 1917-1919. (Folder 166: 17)
    See also Price fixing
  - Pellagra, 1918 (Folder 166: 18)
  - Penalties.
    See 44-H; License revocation and penalties
  - Peptone.
  - Percy, Lord Eustace.
    See Great Britain, Washington Embassy
  - Perishable foods.
  - Persia, 1918 (Folder 166: 19)
  - Personnel of Food Administration photographs.
  - Peru, 1911-1918 (Folder 166: 20)
  - Pharazyn, G.N.
  - Phelan, James D., 1917-1918 (Folder 167: 1)
  - Phelps, R.C.
  - Philippine Islands, 1917-1918 (Folder 167: 2)
  - Phillips, William.
  - Phosphates and acid phosphates, 1917-1918. (Folder 167: 3)
    See also Exports, Superphosphates, Post War Trade and Reconstruction, Scandinavia; Post War Trade, Sweden
  - Pinchot, Gifford.
  - Pine tar, 1917 (Folder 167: 4)
  - Platinum, 1918 (Folder 167: 5)
  - Platt, Charles A.
  - Poetry and Jungles, 1917-1919 (Folder 167: 6-8)
  - Poland, 1917-1919. (Folder 167: 9)
  - Polk, Frank L.
  - Population, 1917-1918 (Folder 167: 10)
  - Puerto Rico.
    See 6-H; 44-H
  - Ports.
    See Shipping, Ports
  - Portugal, 1917-1919 (Folder 167: 11-12)
  - Posey, C. J.
    See Meat
  - Post Office Department, 1917-1918 (Folder 167: 13)
  - Postal rules and regulations, 1917-1918 (Folder 167: 14)
  - Post war trade and reconstruction, 1918. (Folder 167: 15)
    See also Germany, Post War Trade and Reconstruction
  - Potash, potassium, potassium salts, chlorates, and salt, 1917-1918 (Folder 167: 16-17)
  - Potatoes.
    See Vegetables
  - Powell, G. Harold.
  - President Wilson.
    See White House
  - Press articles, 1917-1918. (Folder 167: 18-20)
  - Price fixing, 1917-1928. (Folder 168: 1-5)
    See also Council of National Defense, Wheat Guaranty Grain Corporation, Memo regarding Grain Corporation Price Stabilization and Especially Activities of George N. Peek
  - Price reporters.
  - Price stabilization.
    See Price fixing
  - Prices, 1905-1921
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 168: 6-13)
    - Bread, 1917-1918 (Folder 168: 14)
    - Canned food, 1916-1917 (Folder 168: 15)
    - Coal, copper, iron, and steel, 1911-1917 (Folder 168: 16)
    - Cotton, 1908-1918 (Folder 168: 17)
    - Eggs, 1917-1918 (Folder 168: 18)
    - Fair prices, 1917-1918 (Folder 168: 19)
    - Fats and oils, 1917-1918 (Folder 168: 20)
    - Feeding stuffs, 1911-1918 (Folder 168: 21)
    - Fish, 1917-1918 (Folder 168: 22)
    - Fruit, 1918 (Folder 168: 23)
    - General Index Numbers of Food Prices on a Nutritive Value Base, 1918.
    - Grain, 1909-1919 (Folder 169)
      - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 169: 1)
      - Producers, 1917-1918 (Folder 169: 2)
      - Barley, 1909-1918 (Folder 169: 3)
      - Corn, cornmeal, and corn syrup, 1908-1918 (Folder 169: 4)
      - Oats and oatmeal, rice, and rye, 1908-1918 (Folder 169: 5)
      - Wheat, price of wheat to farmers as fixed by government, 1919 (Folder 169: 6)
    - Livestock, 1911-1918 (Folder 169: 7)
    - Maximum margins, 1918 (Folder 169: 8)
    - Meat, 1905-1918 (Folder 169)
      - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 169: 9)
      - Beef, 1917-1918 (Folder 169: 10)
      - Pork and pork products, 1909-1918 (Folder 169: 11)
      - Poultry, 1909-1917 (Folder 169: 12)
    - New Price Index, 1917.
    - Relative prices farmer and retailer indices, 1909-1918 (Folder 169: 13)
    - Relative prices hogs and corn, 1905-1918 (Folder 169: 14)
    - Retail, 1917-1921 (Folder 169)
      - Comparison of retail food prices as reported to the U.S. Food Administration and the Bureau of Labor, 1917-1919 (Folder 169: 15)
      - Retail Prices; 1913 to December, 1919, bulletin of the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics, Washington, 1921 (Folder 169: 16)
      - United States and Canada, 1917-1918 (Folder 169: 17)
    - Sisal and Manila hemp, 1914-1917 (Folder 169: 18)
    - Wholesale, 1911-1919 (Folder 169)
      - General, 1911-1918 (Folder 169: 19)
      - Wholesale Prices; 1890 to 1919, bulletin of the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics, Washington, 1920 (Folder 169: 20)
      - Post war, 1911-1919 (Folder 169: 21)
      - A Comparison of Wholesale Prices in Great Britain and the United States, bulletin of the Statistical Division Information Service, 1918 (Folder 169: 22)
    - Wholesale and retail, 1917-1919 (Folder 170: 1)
  - Priebe, W. F.
  - Priorities.
    See Programs, Priorities, War Industries Board, Priorities Division, World Trade Board, Priorities Division
  - Prisoners of war, 1916-1918. (Folder 170: 2)
    See also Germany, Alien enemy regulations
  - Profiteering, 1917-1918. (Folder 170: 3)
    See also Federal Trade Commission
  - Programs, 1915-1918. (Folder 170: 4)
    See also Purchases, Shipments and arrivals
  - Prohibition. (Folder 170)
    See War prohibition
  - Propaganda, German, 1916-1918 (Folder 170: 5)
  - Public Health Service, 1917. (Folder 170: 6)
    See also 1-H; Advisory Committee on Public Health International Health Board
  - Public Information Committee. (Folder 170)
    See Committee on Public Information
  - Publicity, 1917-1919. (Folder 170: 7-8)
  - Pugh, Edmund W.
    See 14-H; 37-H
  - Pulitzer, Ralph.
  - Pyrites.
    See Sulphur, etc.
  - Q correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 170: 9)
  - Quick, Herbert.
  - Quinan Henry B.
  - Quinine and chinchona bark, 1918 (Folder 170: 10)
  - R correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 170: 11-17)
  - R correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 171: 1-2)
  - Railroad administration, 1917-1919 (Folder 171)
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 171: 3-4)
    - General Director W. G. McAdoo, 1918. (Folder 171: 5)
      See also Treasury Department
    - Edward Chambers, 1918 (Folder 171: 6)
    - Orders and circulars, 1917-1919 (Folder 171: 7-8)
  - Rathbone, Albert.
  - Rathenau, Walther, The New Economy Policy, 1919 (Folder 171: 9)
  - Ration experiments, 1916 (Folder 171: 10)
  - Rations, 1917-1918. (Folder 171)
    See also World Trade Board Research Bureau, Rationing, Northern Russia, Latin America, Army, Food Rations in the Belligerent Armies on the Western Front, France
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 171: 11-12)
    - Army and Navy, 1918 (Folder 171: 13)
    - Correspondence, 1918 (Folder 171: 14)
  - Raw Materials Control, by A. E. Taylor, circa 1918 (Folder 171: 15)
  - Raymond, C.E.
  - Reading Lord.
  - Reed, James, senator, 1917-1922 (Folder 171: 16)
  - Red Cross.
  - Redfield, Wm. C.
    See Commerce Department
  - Replogle, J. Leonard.
    See War Industries Board, Steel Division
  - Reports, 1917-1940. (Folder 171)
    See also 10-H Daily Reports and Mail Resume, 19-H Report of Expenditures and Budget Data Reports
    - U.S. Food Administration and the U.S. Fuel Administration for the Year 1917, Washington, 1918 (Folder 171: 17)
    - Purchases and Disbursements Made by the U.S. Food Administration and by the U.S. Fuel Administration...From August 11 to December 31, 1917, Washington, 1918 (Folder 172: 1)